troostwijkauctions.com 2007-10-11

# Troostwijk Veilingen en Taxaties

|  |  You are not logged in       \-       Login       \-       Register  
---  
| 

** Privacy Statement**

|   
---|---  

This website is managed by Troostwijk Veilingen B.V. During your visit to this website Troostwijk Veilingen can collect personal details about you, both directly (via a request for your personal details) and indirectly. Troostwijk Veilingen will use these personal details solely for the purposes stated in this Privacy Statement and take the necessary measures to protect the personal details collected.   
  
** Purposes of the Personal Details **  

Troostwijk Veilingen collects and processes details about customers and visitors to this website for its business operations, in order to bring attention to its products and services and to allow you access to whatever of these you find important, and to develop web statistics. The information provided by you can be used to take up contact with you: for example, to inform you of changes in the functionality of the website or to offer you services or products that you might appreciate (unless you have indicated that you do not wish to receive any notice of offers regarding services or products).   
  
** Cookies**  
  
Troostwijk Veilingen can collect and analyze information about the use of this website, inclusive of the domain name, the number of hits, the pages visited, the previous and following websites visited and the length of the user session. These details can be collected by means of a cookie. A cookie is a small text file that our webpage server places on your hard drive. If desired, you may allow or not allow the cookies by changing the settings on your browser. A cookie will make use of the website faster and easier.   
  
** Internet sites of others **  
  
This Privacy Statement does not apply to websites of others who are connected to this website through links.   
  
** Exercise of Rights **  

If you do not wish to receive any marketing information from Troostwijk Veilingen B.V., you can make this known through the personal settings on MyTroostwijk.   
  
** Questions **  

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our activities with regard to processing the details or your use of this website, you may contact us via the e-mail address: info@troostwijkauctions.com, or by ordinary post: Troostwijk Veilingen B.V., Overschiestraat 59, 1062 XD Amsterdam, the Netherlands.   
  
** Amendments to the Privacy Statement **  

Troostwijk Veilingen reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Statement. It is recommended that you consult the Privacy Statement regularly, so that you will be aware of such amendments.   
  
_ © Troostwijk Veilingen January 2007_  
  
|  | 25/4/2007   
De Eendracht in top 10 Insolvencies in 2006   
Read more  
---  
| 15/2/2007   
Sale of the complete plant for DVD/CD production to Middle East.   
Read more  
---
